American Civil Liberties Union Records: Subgroup 2, Organizational Matters Series, 1947-1995: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 1: Organizational Matters, 1930-1995; 582 boxes
  - Subseries 1E.3: Departments: Associate Director Alan Reitman, 1948-1989; 56 boxes
    - Subject Files, 1963-1989; portion of 12 boxes
      - Moral Majority, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 7)
      - Morgan, Charles, 1976; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 8)
      - Musical Majority- requests for information, 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 303, Folder 9-10)
      - Nadel, Mark: Two papers on Cable Television and First Amendment, 1982; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 11)
      - National Advisory Council (NAC), 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 12)
      - National Advisory Council--Ramsey Clark letter, 1977; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 13)
      - National Advisory Council--questionnaire, 1977; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 14)
      - National Association of Broadcasters, 1977; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 1)
      - National Coalition Against Censorship (NCAC), 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 2)
      - National Coalition Against Censorship- Pico and Bicknell decs, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 3)
      - National Coalition Against Censorship (NCAC), 1980-1982; 2 folders (Box 304, Folder 4-5)
      - Nazi Party- Skokie, Illinois, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 6)
      - Oral History of the ACLU: Betsy Brinson, Diane Bowers, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 7)
      - PEARL (National Coalition for Public Education and Religious Liberty), 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 8)
      - Political asylum language, 1986; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 1)
      - Polygraph tests, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 2)
      - Pornography: Children and Policies, 1977-1984; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 3)
      - Pornography, 1983-1985; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 4)
      - Poverty and Civil Liberties, 1973; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 5)
      - Presidential War Powers, 1984; 1987; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 6)
      - President's Commission for a National Agenda for the Eighties, 1980; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 7)
      - Press Access to Military Combat, 1984; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 8)
      - Prison Reform, 1984; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 9)
      - Puerto Rico affiliate: Roger Baldwin correspondence, 1978-1982; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 10)
      - Reitman, Alan, "The ACLU- Today and Tomorrow", 1963; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 11)
      - San Diego affiliate's use of porn film for fund-raising..., 1979; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 12)
      - Religious use of public schools, Policy #95, 1984; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 1)
      - Reproductive freedom, 1984-1985; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 2)
      - Rosenbergs: Disclosure of information and access to the Federal Bureau of Investigation files, 1977; 1983; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 3)
      - Science and Civil Liberties, 1975-1978; 2 folders (Box 306, Folder 4-5)
      - Secular humanism, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 6)
      - Seiler, Lauren and James Murtha: research using human subjects, 1979; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 7)
      - Sex education, 1981; 1989; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 8)
      - Skokie, Illinois: after the controversy, 1980; 1981; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 9)
      - Smoking, 1977; 1986; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 10)
      - Teamsters' trusteeship suit, 1987-1988; 2 folders (Box 307, Folder 1-2)
      - Television in the courtroom, 1984-1986; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 3)
      - Union goods and services, 1981-1986; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 4)
      - Unisex insurance: ACLU policy, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 5)
      - Violence on television, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 6)
      - Voter registration, 1977; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 7)
      - Wulf, Mel- resignation, 1977; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 8)
      - Zionism, 1975; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 9)
      - Zoning, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 1E.4: Departments: Assistant Director Dorothy Dunbar Bromley, 1948-1963; 13 boxes
    The Dorothy Dunbar Bromley subseries (5.88 linear feet) documents her tenure as assistant director of the American Civil Liberties Union. The materials are divided into three groupings: Academic Freedom, Church and State, and Radio/TV.
    The Academic Freedom material primarily covers administrative matters related to academic freedom issues from 1962. The files follow the organizational scheme of the Academic Freedom Subject Files (boxes 722-747), and the materials are primarily composed of memoranda, reports, and newspaper clippings.
    The Church and State materials are grouped under three headings: Education, Public Issues and Religious Organizations, though all contain correspondence, memoranda, minutes, policy statements, press clippings, and publications. Bromley served as executive officer of the ACLU Church and State Committee from 1960-1962; the files contain her correspondence with national and affiliate staff members, board members, staff members of outside organizations, and the general public. Some issues discussed include: Bible reading in public schools, the Regents' prayer case in New York state, bus transportation, federal aid to sectarian schools and colleges, religious holiday observances in public schools, and the Army and Air Force Character Guidance Programs. The Church and State Public Issues heading includes materials on religious observances on public property, Sunday Blue Laws, tax exemption for sectarian schools, problems of conscience and religious freedom, and Leo Pfeffer's resignation from the Church and State Committee in October 1961. The Church and State Religious Organizations heading comprises printed materials and Bromley's correspondence with organizations such as the American Jewish Congress, the American Humanist Association, the Baptist Joint Committee on Public Affairs, the National Conference of Christians and Jews (NCCJ), the Department of Religious Liberty, National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S.A., and Protestants and Other Americans United for the Separation of Church and State.
    The Radio/TV files parallel the organizational scheme of the Mass Communications subject files. Topics covered include: equal time, the Federal Communications Commission, the fairness doctrine, news coverage, licensing, pay TV, programming, public service, and UHF. Materials are composed of memoranda, reports, and various printed materials.
    - Alaska, 1961; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 1)
    - American Council for Judaism, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 2)
    - American Freedoms Council, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 3)
    - American Freedoms Council: Liberal Catholics, 1961; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 4)
    - American Humanist Association, 1957-1962; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 5)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1960; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 6)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1958-1961; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 7)
    - Amish, 1960-1963; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report: Uncut Version, 1960; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 9)
    - Armed Forces: Miscellaneous, 1960; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 10)
    - Army and Air Force: Character Guidance Programs, 1956-1958; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 11)
    - Army and Air Force: Character Guidance Programs, 1951-1952; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 12)
    - Baccalaureate Services, 1957-1962; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 13)
    - Baptist Public Affairs, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 14)
    - Bennett, Dean John C., Union Theological Seminary, 1961; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 15)
    - Bible Distribution, 1956-1961; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 16)
    - Bible Reading in Public Schools, 1957-1961; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 17)
    - Bibliography, 1961; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 18)
    - Biennial Conference, 1962; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 19)
    - Bierstedt, Dr. Robert: Address at ACLU Biennial Conference, 1962; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 20)
    - Blacksburg, VA Public Schools, 1961; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 21)
    - Blanshard, Paul: Correspondence, 1962; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous: British Broadcasting Co, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 1)
    - Brown, Ralph S.: Address at ACLU Biennial Conference, 1962; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 2)
    - Bus Transportation, 1957-1961; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 3)
    - Campus Unrest: Elmira College Warning to Students Re: Sympathy, 1960; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 4)
    - Campus Unrest: Sit-Ins, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 5)
    - "Captive" Schools (Public Schools Merged with Parochial Schools), 1961; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 6)
    - Carr and Catto v. St. John's University: NYCLU, 1962; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 7)
    - Cases: Berkman v. Mississippi Southern College, 1959; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 8)
    - Cases: Central Michigan Dismissal, 1960; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 9)
    - Cases: Colony v. Dusquene University, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 10)
    - Cases: De Haan Case, 1959; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 11)
    - Cases: Fifth Amendment Cases, 1957-1959; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 12)
    - Cases: Gara, 1962; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 13)
    - Cases: George Washington University Reichard Case, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 14)
    - Cases: Gottlieb v. Liberman, 1959; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 15)
    - Cases: Hamilton - Tuskegee, 1960; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 16)
    - Cases: Jerome, 1960; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 17)
    - Cases: Jerome, 1962; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 18)
    - Cases: Junker, 1961; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 19)
    - Cases: Krochmal, 1959-1961; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 20)
    - Cases: Leader, 1959; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 21)
    - Cases: McDaniel v. Texas, 1960; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 22)
    - Cases: Merchant New York University, 1958; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 23)
    - Cases: Monmouth College Case, 1959; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 1)
    - Cases: Picarello - University of Maryland, 1956-1962; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 2)
    - Cases: Reddick, 1960; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 3)
    - Catholic Colleges, 1962; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 4)
    - Catholic Viewpoints, 1957-1962; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 5)
    - Censorship, 1960; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 6)
    - Census: U.S., 1958-1961; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 7)
    - Chapel Attendance at Air Force Academy, 1959; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 8)
    - Chapels and Chaplains, etc, 1956-1962; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous: Chicago Television Hearings, FCC, 1962; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 10)
    - Christian Amendment, 1962; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 11)
    - Churches and Politics, 1960; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 12)
    - Cincinnati Chapter, 1960; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 13)
    - College Courses, 1960; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 14)
    - Colorado Affiliate: Boulder Public Schools, Religious Holiday, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 15)
    - Congressional Committees (Church and State), 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 16)
    - Conscience, Problems of, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 17)
    - Court Sentence (Compulsory Church as Punishment), 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 18)
    - Criticism, Letters of, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 19)
    - Custody of Children, 1958; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 20)
    - Discrimination, 1957-1960; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 21)
    - Dormitory Loans, 1961; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 22)
    - Draft Pamphlet, Church-State (Never Used), 1948; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 23)
    - Education: American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1959-1963; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 1)
    - Education: Arizona, 1961; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 2)
    - Education: Board of Foreign Scholarships, 1960-1963; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 3)
    - Education: College Student Pamphlet Correspondence, 1961; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 4)
    - Education: Cornell Graduate Students Rights, 1960-1963; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 5)
    - Education: Correspondence to National Defense Education Act, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 6)
    - Education: Fund for Social Analysis, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 7)
    - Education: Kentucky State College, 1960; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 8)
    - Education: Louisiana State University, 1959; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 9)
    - Education: Lowenstein, 1955-1960; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 10)
    - Education: Lynchburg College, 1960; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 11)
    - Education: Mississippi University, 1963; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 12)
    - Education: National Defense Education Act (NDEA), 1958-1960; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 13)
    - Education: NDEA Hearings, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 14)
    - Education: National Science Foundation, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 15)
    - Education: Negro Educational Review, 1961; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 16)
    - Education: Northern Kansas City School District, 1960; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 17)
    - Education: Olson, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 1)
    - Education: Protests Against, 1959-1962; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 2)
    - Education: Smith College, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 3)
    - Education: Southern Regional Council, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 4)
    - Education: State of Louisiana, 1961; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 5)
    - Education: United Fruit Company, Accreditation, 1960; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 6)
    - Education: University of New Hampshire, 1961; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 7)
    - Education: Withdrawal of Universities from NDEA, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 8)
    - Election Coverage: Yarborough Watchdog Bill, 1961; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 9)
    - Enlistee's Oath, 1961; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 10)
    - Equal Time: Gould, Jack, 1960; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 11)
    - Equal Time: Socialist Labor Party, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 12)
    - Equal Time: Socialist Workers, 1960; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 13)
    - Equal Time: Miscellaneous, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 14)
    - Equal Time for Political Candidates, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 15)
    - "Extent of Religious Influence in American Public Schools", 1961; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 16)
    - Fairness Doctrine: American Medical Association, 1962; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 17)
    - Fairness Doctrine: Anti-Communist Programs, 1957; 1962; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 1)
    - Fairness Doctrine: Arizona Affiliate, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 2)
    - Fairness Doctrine: Guest Stars, 1961; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 3)
    - Fairness Doctrine: Miscellaneous, 1962; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 4)
    - FCC: Fee, 1962; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 5)
    - Federal Aid, 1961; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 6)
    - Federal Support for Construction of Academic and Housing Facilities, 1961; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 7)
    - Flag Salute, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 8)
    - Florida Affiliate, 1962; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 9)
    - Fund for Research and Education: ACLU Statements, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 10)
    - Fund for Research and Education: Bibliography of Academic Freedom, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 11)
    - Fund for Research and Education: Contract Work, 1959-1961; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 12)
    - Fund for Research and Education: Corporate Structure and Academic, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 13)
    - Fund for Research and Education: Correspondence with Trustees, 1959; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 14)
    - Fund for Research and Education: Effect of Desegregation Controversy, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 15)
    - Fund for Research and Education: Freedom of Knowledge and Movement, 1959-1961; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 16)
    - Fund for Research and Education: General, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 17)
    - Fund for Research and Education: General, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 1)
    - Fund for Research and Education: Publications, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 2)
    - Fund for Research and Education: Report, 1959; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 3)
    - Fund for Research and Education: Subcommittee Reports, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 4)
    - Fund for Research and Education: Trustees Minutes, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 5)
    - Garb of Teachers, 1958-1961; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 6)
    - General, 1959-1962; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 7)
    - General: includes Miscellaneous publications, 1949-1962; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 8)
    - Gym Teachers, 1960; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 9)
    - Heald Commission Report, New York, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 10)
    - Legislation: General, 1959-1962; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 11)
    - Legislation: New York County Lawyers Association, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 12)
    - Licensing: Oregon, 1960; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 13)
    - Licensing: Westinghouse Broadcasting, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 14)
    - Loyalty Oath: New York City Oath for High School Students, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 1)
    - Loyalty Oaths: General, 1960; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 2)
    - Members, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 3)
    - Miami, Florida: Bible Reading and Religious Observances in Public, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 4)
    - Minority Political Parties Air Time, 1960; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 5)
    - Minow, Newton N., Chairman, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous: National Association of Broadcasters: Collins, Leroy, 1961; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 7)
    - National Capitol Area Affiliate, 1962; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 8)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews (NCCJ), 1961; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 9)
    - National Council of Churches of Christ: Dept. of Religious Liberties, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 10)
    - National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S.A.: General, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 11)
    - National Student Christian Federation: Division of National Council..., 1960; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 12)
    - New Jersey Affiliate, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 13)
    - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU); Critique of "Moral and...", 1955-1956; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 14)
    - News Coverage: Court Coverage Bans, 1958-1960; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 15)
    - News Coverage: National Broadcasting Company, 1961; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 16)
    - News Releases, 1961; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 17)
    - Niagara Frontier Branch Affiliates, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 18)
    - Northern California Affiliate, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 19)
    - Notre Dame University, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 20)
    - Ohio Affiliates, Cleveland and Toledo: Northwest Ohio, 1959-1962; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 21)
    - Oregon Affiliate: Textbook Law Case, Nativity Scene Protest, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 1)
    - Overseas Dependents' Schools, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 2)
    - Parochial Schools and Parochial School Texts, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 3)
    - Pay/TV, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 4)
    - Peace Corps, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 5)
    - Pfeffer, Leo: Resignation from Church-State Committee, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 6)
    - Philadelphia Affiliate, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 7)
    - Policy Statements: 1942, 1946, 1952, 1955, 1957-1962 various, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 8)
    - Population Multiplier: Federal Aid, 1961; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 9)
    - Potential Cases and Developments, 1960; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 10)
    - Prayers, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 11)
    - Presbyterian Church, 1958-1962; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 12)
    - Presidential Election, 1960; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 13)
    - Programming: Diversity, 1960; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 14)
    - Programming: Illinois Affiliate, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 15)
    - Programming: Miscellaneous, 1958-1961; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 16)
    - Protestant Council of the City of New York, 1961; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 17)
    - Protestant Statements and Views, 1959-1961; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 18)
    - Protestants and Other Americans United (POAU), 1957-1961; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 1)
    - Public: General, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 2)
    - Public Questionnaires Concerning Religion, 1957; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 3)
    - Public Service: Educational TV, 1961; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 4)
    - Public Service: Public Interest Groups, 1959; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 5)
    - Puerto Rico, 1961; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 6)
    - Pulse Incorporated, 1961; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 7)
    - Quotas, 1955-1956; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 8)
    - Regents' Prayer Case (Long Island, NY), 1959-1962; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 9)
    - Regents' Prayer Case (Letters), 1962; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 10)
    - Released Time, 1957-1960; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 11)
    - Religion Panel Meeting Agenda and Minutes, 1955-1958; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 12)
    - Religious Displays on Public Property, 1957-1961; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 13)
    - Religious Freedom Committee, Inc, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 14)
    - Religious Garb, 1961; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 15)
    - Religious Holiday Observances, 1961; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 16)
    - Religious Observances on Public Property and Related Issues, 1959-1961; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 1)
    - Religious Revival, 1957; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 2)
    - Religious Training in Schools, 1958-1961; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 3)
    - Rhode Island Affiliate, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 4)
    - Right-Wing Attacks, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 5)
    - St. Louis Civil Liberties Committee, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 6)
    - Schempp Case: Constitutionality of Pennsylvania statute on Bible reading, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 7)
    - School Libraries, 1960; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 8)
    - School Lunch Act, 1962; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 9)
    - Sectarian Colleges, Support of, 1958-1960; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 10)
    - Sectarian Schools, Support of, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 11)
    - Senate Subcommittee on Constitutional Rights (Hennings Committee), 1955; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 12)
    - Shared Time, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 13)
    - Specific Protests against Government Actions, 1955; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 14)
    - Staff Members, 1961; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 15)
    - "The State and Sectarian Education," Research Division, National, 1956; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 16)
    - State Statutes and Constitutions, 1958-1961; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 17)
    - Statistics, 1960; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 18)
    - Students: Discipline, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 19)
    - Students: Discrimination in Classroom, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 20)
    - Students: Foreign Students, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 21)
    - Students: General, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 22)
    - Students: National Student Association, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 319, Folder 1)
    - Students: Publication Supervision, University of Delaware, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 319, Folder 2)
    - Students: Scholarship Denials, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 319, Folder 3)
    - Students: Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 319, Folder 4)
    - Studies of Church and State: Miscellaneous, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 319, Folder 5)
    - Sunday Blue Laws, 1958-1962; 1 folder (Box 319, Folder 6)
    - Supreme Court Decisions, 1950; 1960; 1 folder (Box 319, Folder 7)
    - The Tablet, "Pro and Con on the ACLU", 1962; 1 folder (Box 319, Folder 8)
    - Tax Exemption: Private Welfare Agencies, 1961; 1 folder (Box 319, Folder 9)
    - Tax Exemption Denial: Washington, D.C. Ethical Society, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Box 319, Folder 10)